Friday night Donald Trump announced the
u.s. was launching airstrikes against
chemical weapons facilities in Syria in
response the gas attacks by Syrian
President Bashar al-assad against his
own people the purpose of our actions
tonight is to establish a strong
deterrent against the production spread
and use of chemical weapons let me say
up front news from the Middle East is
kind of like hearing a woman talking
about The Bachelor like I know it
involves a lot of people I know nothing
about and they're always fighting and
and the use of chemicals has resulted in
people getting hurt Assad used chemical
weapons on his own people the US can't
sit idly by as Assad commits such
atrocities plus the bombing was backed
by France and Britain so this wasn't a
madman
acting alone it was a madman plus I want
to say Dame Judi Dench and her tennis
instructor the problem is Trump can't do
anything without being so Trumpy about
it
president Trump taunting Russia ahead of
potential US airstrikes in Syria the
president just tweeted this Russia vows
to shoot down any and all missiles fired
at Syria
get ready Russia because they will be
coming nice and new and smart yeah of
course they knew then missiles missiles
at something you can reuse over and over
again they're not condoms
now no I don't reuse him for sex that
would be ridiculous I use them as
punching bags to train my hamster he
he's got a big fight coming up you gotta
eat parts and flight-deck fired up
either the the beaver is the equivalent
of a tiger in his world also rule number
one of shit-talking is you can't talk
and then the next day pretend you
weren't talking the day before
after yesterday saying that missiles
were coming he's now back on Twitter
clarifying that maybe they're not coming
as soon as people thought here's what he
said never said when an attack on Syria
would take place could be very soon or
not soon at all what does that mean when
does the president the United States
become a troll telling riddles
underneath a bridge Billy Dee will play
our part with missiles nice and new and
smart here they come or do they go and
when they do you'll never know travelers
been thinking about Syria for a while in
2013 when President Obama was also
considering bombing Syria Trump insisted
he needed congressional approval so in
Trump or the strikes on Friday yeah he
didn't get congressional approval while
Assad's chemical weapons use was
horrific
Congress never authorized the u.s. to
attack a country that has not attacked
us this is further example of Donald
Trump in his administration not
following the Constitution and not
following the rule of law I've never
really understood that I don't get has
some war is legal and some isn't like
how dare you use chemical weapons when
I'm shooting at you we're trying to have
a good honest murdering of each other
and you started cheating
why can't you just kill your country's
people the American Way
by putting let in their water hello to
all of our viewers in Flint I think it
was the right decision to retaliate
against Assad but it's hard to give
Trump credit because let's be honest
Trump doesn't really care about the
people of Syria some of the criticism
following the strikes in Syria involved
the current US policy regarding Syrian
refugees
barring in their entry into this country
here are the latest numbers in 2016
15,000 479 Syrian refugees enter this
country in 2018 so far 11 that's that's
what you call a reduced number see we
can't go into a country and stop blowing
stuff up if we aren't going to help the
refugees we're creating in the process
France and Britain are taking in as many
as 30,000 refugees and Germany is taking
in a million Germany
good for you Germany nice effort but we
still remember what you did
[Applause]
we're barely taking in 11 Syrian
refugees this year 11 I've had a
doctor's finger in my ass more than 11
times way more
well they say they're doctors and I
don't know why they work at the back of
a food truck and normally doctors don't
work in groups but anyway my point is
until the United States start taking in
hundreds of refugees it seems like my
is more tolerant than this
country
[Music]